- A Digital Machine Learning Algorithm Simulating Spiking Neural Network CoLaNET
- A Unified Geometric Field Theory Framework for Transformers: From Manifold Embeddings to Kernel Modulation
- AAAI Workshop on AI Planning for Cyber-Physical Systems -- CAIPI24
- An Incomplete Loop: Instruction Inference, Instruction Following, and In-context Learning in Language Models
- Comment on "Black hole in Dehnen $(1,\,4,\,\frac{1}{2})$ dark matter halo: exact solution, lensing, light ring, and thermodynamics (EPJC 85 (2025) 1256)"
- Exact Sparse Orthogonal Dictionary Learning
- FQ-PETR: Fully Quantized Position Embedding Transformation for Multi-View 3D Object Detection
- IDEA: Enhancing the Rule Learning Ability of Large Language Model Agent through Induction, Deduction, and Abduction
- Image Quality Assessment: Investigating Causal Perceptual Effects with Abductive Counterfactual Inference
- Monotone Neural Control Barrier Certificates
- PARADISE: Evaluating Implicit Planning Skills of Language Models with Procedural Warnings and Tips Dataset
- PRISM-Bench: A Benchmark of Puzzle-Based Visual Tasks with CoT Error Detection
- Probabilistic Abduction for Visual Abstract Reasoning via Learning Rules in Vector-symbolic Architectures
- Proceedings Twentieth Conference on Theoretical Aspects of Rationality and Knowledge
- Proceedings of the First International Workshop on Next-Generation Language Models for Knowledge Representation and Reasoning (NeLaMKRR 2024)
- Proceedings of the Second International Workshop on Next-Generation Language Models for Knowledge Representation and Reasoning (NeLaMKRR 2025)
- Reasoning Like a Doctor: Improving Medical Dialogue Systems via Diagnostic Reasoning Process Alignment
- Reconstruction of Compressively Sensed Images using Convex Tikhonov Sparse Dictionary Learning and Adaptive Spectral Filtering
- Robust Vector Quantized-Variational Autoencoder
- Towards Learning to Reason: Comparing LLMs with Neuro-Symbolic on Arithmetic Relations in Abstract Reasoning
- Variationally Consistent Framework for Finite-Strain Microelasticity
